ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Regional Economic Development
  - Seeing 2020: Business Leader Focus Group Jul 2, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Seeing 2020: Joint Report September 9, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Vision to Action September 23, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Champions Renewed, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Working on a High Road Economy July 11, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - GM - Euro Works Conference November 2005 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Labor Leader in Residence, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Labor in Action Annual Meeting, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo, 2003-2007 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Picture; Berkshire Hathaway Inc. Annual Report
  - Self - Sufficiency Coalition, 2003-2006 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    SEEDCO Informational Folder
  - Buffalo Labor Studies: Local Economic Development April 17, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Champions at Work Executive Summary
  - Citizens Communications: CWA, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Grassroots Economic Development Group, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    2004 Agenda
  - Economic Development Initiatives Report to Resident - Extension Committee July 8, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Extra Materials for Buffalo Labor Studies Class in Economic Development (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Economic Development Initiative (EDI) September 2-3, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Economic Development Initiative (EDI) Website, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Economic Development Initiative (EDI) Report, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Working Women Conference March 28, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Erie Niagara Regional Partnership, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - University at Buffalo Outreach, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Building Workforce Partnerships Conference Materials May 2004 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Workforce Investment Board Conference, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Series J: Empire State Poll (ESP) and Regional Development
  - Empire State Poll (ESP), 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Program October 22, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    ESP Report
  - Empire State Poll (ESP): Participation Study, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) and Survey Research Institute (SRI), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Meeting Agenda: Charts
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Binder (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Binder (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    SRI Informational Folder
  - Empire State Poll (ESP), 2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Report, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    ILR SRI Informational Folder
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Binder, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Stem Cell Research, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Empire State Poll (ESP) Report, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Series K: Early Childhood Education Project
  - Child Care Study, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Resource Guide for Workplace and Family Issues
  - Child Care September 2006 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Child Care July 2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Child Care Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Informational Folder
  - Child Care November 2006 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Child Care Means Business (Folder 1 of 2), 2006 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Child Care Means Business (Folder 2 of 2), 2006 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Child Care Means Business Binder September 7, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Presentation Slides
  - Early Childhood Education and Economic Development Binder N 30, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Nurses United Daycare (Folder 1 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Nurses United Daycare (Folder 2 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Nurses United Daycare (Folder 3 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Child Care Study, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - The Child Care Coalition of the Niagara Frontier (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Series L: Miscellaneous Programs
  - LOCNES (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - LOCNES (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - LOCNES (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo Studies Group, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Council for International Visitors, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Western New York Economic Development Corporation (WNYEDC), 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Western New York Economic Development Corporation (WNYEDC) Statistic Training Partnership (STP), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - City of Buffalo Project (Folder 1 of 4), 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - City of Buffalo Project (Folder 2 of 4), 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Cartoons about work; Report
  - City of Buffalo Project (Folder 3 of 4), 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - City of Buffalo Project (Folder 4 of 4), 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    February issue of The Buffalo News; Harvard business review
  - Buffalo Community Studies Group, 1977-1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Government Task Force: State of the Region Project (Folder 1 of 2), 1989-1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Government Task Force: State of the Region Project (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Institute for Local Governance and Regional Growth Folders
  - H. Carl McCall: Regional Cooperation (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Erie County Consolidation (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Erie County Consolidation (Folder 2 of 2), 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Erie County Consolidation Phase III, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Western New York Economy Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 1 of 5), 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 2 of 5), 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Leaning, Growing & Sharing Together Folder
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 3 of 5), 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Informational Folder; AQP issue
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 4 of 5), 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 5 of 5), 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    ILR Information; AQP Conference Pamphlet
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 1 of 3), 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Center for Team Performance Folder
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 2 of 3), 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Western New York Employee Involvement Council (Folder 3 of 3), 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Competitive Action Committee Deferiet Mill, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Champion Deferiet's Total Quality Plan (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Champion Deferiet UPIU, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Industry Education Program Folder; Champion International Corporation Annual Report
  - Roswell Park Cancer Institute, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Exolon USWA, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Lynn Williams Visit April 1995 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    January/February issue of SteeLabor
  - Conversations with Thomas Kochan, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Health Care Conference June 1994 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    ILR Folder
  - "Prospering in America" Radio Show, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Prospering in America Folders
  - New York State Industrial Cooperation Council, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Preventing Layoffs Booklet
  - New York Center for Employee Ownership and Partnership (Folder 1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New York Center for Employee Ownership and Partnership (Folder 2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - New York Compact, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Industrial Democracy, 1985-1987 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    Democracy in America Two Day Conference hosted by Rutgers
  - Critical Choices: New Yok and the Constitution Buffalo Niagara Town Meeting June 9, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Two copies of The Constitution
  - Civic Literacy, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - R.P. Adams USWA Local 4447, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    Company Agreement
  - Labor Day Parade, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Northeast-Midwest Alliance of Management and Labor, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - International Team Visit September 21, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - IMF-JC USWA Local 593 Visit May 15, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - NLRP and the Wagner Act October 5-6, 1995, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - PERB and the Taylor Law October 24, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Rich Products, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - AT&T - CWA Articles, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - BorderNet Alliance, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Niagara Environmental Guide
  - International Auto Supplies, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Daimler - Chrysler UAW, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Color Corporation - USWA, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - NABISCO - BCT Union, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - PERB Conferences, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Two ILR Folders
  - O - Cello - USWA, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Career and Education Expo, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - European Research Resources (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Workforce Training: Richard McGahey (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - University at Buffalo Institute for Local Governance and Growth, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Building Productive Workplaces, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Erie County, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Western New York Public Sector Projects, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - City of Buffalo - AFSCME Local 264, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Public Sector Labor - Management Committee, 2002-2006 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - European Community Articles (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - European Community Articles (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - European Community Articles (Folder 3 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - European Community Articles (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 22)
    August Issue of The Economist
  - European Community Articles (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - East European Visit, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Austria (Box 27, Folder 25)
    AW Spezial Issue (German)
  - Europe Project Phase II, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    Institute for Industry Studies
- Series M: Union Work
  - Labor Program Announcements, 1978-1986 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - A Guide to Information on Closely Held Corporations, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Extension of Bargaining Rights and Contracts, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Labor in the 80s, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Unity Day II, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Career and Education Expo, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - District Three Council Meeting and Summer School June 26-28, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Sticker
  - Steel Workers, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Lie Detector Program, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Flyers
  - Local Union Officers Training, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Various informational booklets
  - Phoenix Construction Project (Folder 1 of 3), 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Informational Folder (2)
  - Phoenix Construction Project (Folder 2 of 3), 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Information Folder (2)
  - Phoenix Construction Project (Folder 3 of 3), 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Information Folder
  - Union Statistics for Plant Closings, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Report (3)
  - IUE District 3, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - AFL - CIO Council, 1981-1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Booklet (4)
  - UAW, 1981-1987 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Booklet
  - UAW Leadership Conference Cape May, New Jersey August 22, 1990 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - UAW Leadership Conference Cape May, New Jersey August 22, 1990 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Pie Charts; Overhead Projector Images
  - UAW Doug Fraser Visit November 1990 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Invitations
  - UAW Leadership Conference Black Lake, Michigan November 14, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - UAW Europe Project, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Overhead Slides
  - UAW Summer School, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - UAW Local 686 Retirees June 4, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - UAW Local 501 Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949 (Folder 1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - UAW Local 501 Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949 (Folder 2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Images
  - UAW Local 501 Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949 (Folder 3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - UAW Region 9 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Booklet; Information Folder; Flyers
  - USWA, 1982-1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - USWA Local 1753, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - USWA Local 4447, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - USWA Political Materials, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - USWA 1990 Convention, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - USWA Proposal, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - USWA Legislative Conference June 1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - USWA District 4 Labor Education Project, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - USWA District 4 Summer School June 22-26, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - USWA District 14 Project, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - USWA Civil Rights (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Sexual Harassment Posters
  - USWA in Memoriam, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Funeral Program
  - IBEW Local 41, 1997-2002 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Henry Schiro, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Obituary
  - Local Organizers History, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - What's AFTA NAFTA? April 25-28, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Which Way Labor? Rebuilding the Labor Movement and Labor Education May 17-19, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Booklets
  - UALE Conference March 30 - April 3, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Material from Ron Applegate (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - IRRA Perspective on Work Articles, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Power Building Groups (Folder 1 of 2), 2006 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Power Building Groups (Folder 2 of 2), 2006 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Fiscal Policy Institute, NYS AFL-CIO Economic Development Initiatives, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - NYS AFL- CIO Strategic Research, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - NYS AFL - CIO, 1993-2005 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Workforce Development Institute, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield OPEIU Local 212, 1993-2002 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Outokumpu American Brass USWA Local 593 Drug and Alcohol Programs, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    ILR Information Folder
  - Labor Services, 1994-1999 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Series N: Western Region Administration
  - Cornell ILR Western Region Website, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Basic Planning Documents, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Organization, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Salary Guide
  - Administrative Support System Spring 1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Financial Information December 1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Faculty, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Regional Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Western Region Planning Fall 1997 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Cal Sutliff, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Interpersonal Influence Inventory
  - Catherwood Library, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Industry Studies Faculty Meeting August 21, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Actors Equity Association, 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - University at Buffalo Internship Programs, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Business Plan Work (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Business Plan Work (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Industry Studies Planning, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Staff Research, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Annual and Financial Report Data, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Faculty, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Capilano College Summer Course Roster
  - Faculty Spring and Summer 1998 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Assistant Searches, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Organization Project, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Faculty, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Faculty (Folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Faculty (Folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Support Staff Meeting (Folder 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Support Staff Meeting (Folder 2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Office Reorganization, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Strategic Planning and Historic Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Finance Committee, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Cost Figures (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Institute for Industry Studies Accounting, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Strategic Planning, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Current Finances, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Financial Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Budgets, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Budgets, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Budgets, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Budgets, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Budgets, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Budgets, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Budgets, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Budgets, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Budgets, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Budgets, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Budgets, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Budgets, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Budgets, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Action Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Industry Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Industry Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Institute for Industry Studies Activities, 1987-1993 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Industry Studies Faculty and Administration, 1988-1990 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Handbook Project, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Administration Issues, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Faculty May - June 2002 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Charts; Presentation
  - Faculty Goals, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies and Supervisory Studies Faculty, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Management Development Partnership Team, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Faculty January-April 2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Presentation; Charts
  - Faculty October-December 2001 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Goals, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Administration Spring 2006 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Program Information, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Finances, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Administration June 2001 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Program Evaluations March 2001 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Goals, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Financial Information, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Goals, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Regional Administration, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Staff Meeting February 12, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Goals, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Mailing List, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Industry Studies Proposals, 1996-2000 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Industry Studies, 1989-1995 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Summer Internships, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Martin Manley, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    American Workplace March 1994
- Series O: ILR Extension Administration
  - Extension Directors June 2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Extension Directors January - March 2002 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Institute for Community College Development
  - Extension Directors November-December 2001 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Extension Directors October 2001 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Extension Directors July-August 2001 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Extension Directors April - May 2001 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Extension Directors April 2001 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Program Evaluation March - April 2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Extension Directors March 2001 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Extension Directors October 2000 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Political cartoon
  - Extension Financial Advisory Group, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Extension Directors September 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Extension Directors May 2000 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Extension Directors April 2000 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Extension Directors March - April 2000 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Extension Directors (Folder 1 of 2), 2000 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Extension Directors (Folder 2 of 2), 2000 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Human Resources Champions
  - Marketing Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Extension Directors November1998-May 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Society for Human Resources Management Research
  - Extension Directors March 1999 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Extension Directors January 1999 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Extension Directors, 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Staff Meeting, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Glacial Gift
  - Extension Directors January - April 1998 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    Workers' Art Between Wars
  - Extension Directors September-December 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Committees, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Distance Learning, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Program, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Directors Current Work, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Cartoon
  - Statewide Staff Meeting June 1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Extension Directors Spring 1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Susan Woods' Transfer, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Extension Directors April 1996 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Directors Current Work, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Journal Project, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Extension Directors November 1995 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Extension Directors September 1995 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    ILR Alumni News
  - Extension Directors May 1995 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Service Cycle
  - Search Conference Information, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - HR Ratios, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Extension Directors December 1994 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Extension Directors September 1994 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Union Leadership Institute
  - Cornell Outreach Council, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Postcard
  - Extension Directors January - March 1993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Extension Directors, 1988-1992 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Opportunities Group, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - International Task Force, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Extension Groups and Resources, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    How We Work Goals
  - Credit Revision, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Program Reporting Committee, 1997-2002 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Extension Website, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Extension Website, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    Pictures
  - Extension Website December 1999 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Extension Website November 1999 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Extension Website January-July 1999 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Extension Website, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Series P: Westerr European Organization of te Metal Trades (WEM)
  - Address Information and Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Plastic Sleeve of Business Cards
  - Address Information and Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Lowell Turner Presentation, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Presentation for WEM
  - WEM Program Meetings, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - WEM North American Fact-Finding Tour May 2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - WEM Pre-Tour Binder March 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Buffalo Niagara Enterprise
  - WEM General Information, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - WEM Fabrimetal (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - WEM Fabrimetal (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Fabrimetal CD-ROM
  - Atlantic Corridor, USA (Folder 1 of 2), 2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Corridor, USA (Folder 2 of 2), 2000 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Austria (Box 35, Folder 12)
    German Publication
  - Motorola-Elma, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Strippit LVD (Box 35, Folder 14)
    Information Mailings
  - Niagara Region Movement (Box 35, Folder 15)
    Various Informational Folder; UB Business Management Booklet
  - Outokumpu American Brass (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Informational Folder with a Pin
- Series Q: Corning Glass